乔伊  试镜试得怎么样  超赞的
How did the audition go? Incredible.
我认识了导演  你们一定不会相信导演是谁
I met the director. You'll never believe who it was.
是谁
Who?
给你们一点提示
I'll give you one hint.
华伦比提
Warren Beatty.
哇噢
Wow.
只是可能有个小问题
There's just one thing that might be a problem.
是这样的  我不得不亲一个男人
See, I had to kiss this guy.
因为他帅到不行吗
Because he was just so darn cute?
不是  是试镜过程的一部分  我想争取的角色…
No, part of the audition. I'm up for the part of this guy...
我演和他接吻那部分
...who the main guy kisses.
反正你是演员  咬咬牙就上了吧
Well, you're an actor. I say you just suck it up and you do it.
或者直接上也行
Or you just do it.
我亲了  我很专业
I did do it. I'm a professional.
那问题在哪儿  试镜后…
What's the problem? After the scene...
比提先生过来找我 他说〝演得好  接吻很烂〞
...Mr. Beatty comes up to me and he says, "Good actor. Bad kisser."
你们相信吗  居然说我不是接吻高手
Can you believe that? Me, not a good kisser.
就像在说…
That's like...
德蕾莎修女不是好妈妈一样
...Mother Teresa, not a good mother. Pfft.
谁管那家伙怎么想
Who cares what that guy thinks?
华伦比提哪懂什么叫接吻
What does Warren Beatty know about kissing? Heh.
噢  嘿  嘿
Oh. Heh, heh.
《老友记》 第二季 第24集: 婚礼闹场记
Friends S02E24: The One With Barry and Mindy's Wedding
（主演：詹妮弗·安妮斯顿）
（主演：柯特妮·考克斯）
（主演：丽莎·库卓）
（主演：马特·勒布朗）
（主演：马修·派瑞）
（主演：大卫·修蒙）
你的经纪人怎么说
What did your agent say?
接吻这码子事绝对是关键问题
Yep. This kiss thing is definitely a problem.
比提先生星期一要再看一遍
Mr. Beatty wants to see it again on Monday.
（制片：塔德·史帝文斯）
老天爷  我得找出  自己到底哪里做错
Man, I gotta figure out what I'm doing wrong.
（制片：贝西·伯恩斯）
好  你们哪个女生过来亲我一下
Oh, okay. One of you girls come over here and kiss me.
休想  想得美
Forget it. Yeah, right.
拜托  我需要你们的帮忙
Hey, come on. I need your help here.
我来吧  我以前亲过他  我可以再亲一遍
I'll do it. I've kissed him before. I can do it again.
瞧  这才叫朋友
See this, huh? This is a friend.
开始吧
Uh-huh. Let's go.
等一下  我嘴里有口香糖
Oh, wait. I have gum.
好了
Okay.
很好  非常好  坚定而温柔
Good. Very good. Firm, but tender.
我会跟朋友推荐你
I'd recommend you to a friend.
那我就不知道问题到底在哪儿
Then I don't know what the problem is.
（编剧：布朗·曼德尔）
乔伊  也许你不习惯亲男生
Maybe you're not used to kissing men.
也许你只是太紧张了一点
Maybe you tensed up a little.
（故事：艾拉·安德里德）
也许那才是你该多练习的
Maybe you need to work on it.
没错  有道理
Yeah, that makes sense.
（导演：麦可·连贝克）
除非我死了
Over my dead body.
我会拿他的尸体当挡箭牌
And I'll be using his dead body as a shield.
出来吧  亲爱的  我跟你说  你看起来很美
Come out, honey. I'm telling you, you look good.
快说她看起来很美…告诉她很漂亮
Tell her she looks good. Tell her she looks good.
我的天啊
Oh, my God! Ha, ha, ha.
你看起来真美
You look so good!
我真不敢相信自己  要在两百人面前走上红毯…
I cannot believe I have to walk down the aisle in front of 200 people...
打扮得像恶心想吐时要喝的饮料
...looking like something you drink when you're nauseous.
那别穿了  我不明白我们为什么要去
So don't. I don't see why we have to go to this thing.
反正是你前未婚夫的婚礼
it's your ex-fiance's wedding.
因为我答应敏蒂了
Because I promised Mindy I would.
你不是也答应巴瑞要嫁给他吗
Yeah, well, you promised Barry you'd marry him.
各位  我得走了  我是伴娘
You guys, I have to go. I'm the maid of honor.
除了那次  我只想再见见这些人
Besides, I need to be in a room again with these people...
自己开心就行
...and feel good about myself.
有人还穿着昨天晚上的衣服  很忙吗
Someone's wearing the same clothes they had on last night. Get a little action?
好像是
I may have.
喔呼  种马
Whoo-hoo! Stud!
她长什么样子  我们没见过面
What's she look like? We haven't met.
只是在网上聊了一个通宵
We stayed up all night talking on the Internet.
电脑宅男
Whoo-hoo! Geek!
我喜欢这女生  真的很喜欢这女生
I like this girl. I seriously like this girl.
你们也知道我防卫心强  会讽刺人
You know how I tend to get a little defended and quippy?
哪有  根本没有好吗
Get out. No. Please.
她很直接揭穿我  她说 〝别装了 面对现实吧〞
Well, she called me on it, okay? She said, "Cut it out, get real."
我就是这样做的
And I did.
哇
Wow.
做成什么样子
What's that like?
就像这样  做我自己
It's like this. Me.
不嬉皮笑脸
No jokes.
别说了  你吓到我了
Stop it. You're freaking me out.
没错  我不喜欢这样的你
Yeah. I don't like you this way.
晚点见
I'll see you guys later.
再见  理查  再见
Bye, Richard. Bye-bye.
再见  甜心  我爱你
Bye, sweetie. I love you.
我也爱你
I love you too.
我的男友也让我这么神魂颠倒过
I think my boyfriend's ever so dreamy.
不知道我们的婚礼会是什么样子
I wonder what our wedding will be like.
你说什么啊  什么婚礼
What are you talking about? What wedding?
别装了  你们从没聊过吗
Come on. You never talk about that?
从来没有
No, never.
我们活在当下
We're just living in the moment.
终于不用一直绕着 〝我们未来会怎样〞问题打转
It is so nice for once not to get hung up on, "Where is this going?"
你怕问他吗  怕得要命
Afraid to ask him? Could not be more terrified.
我觉得你该认真考虑下婚姻了
I think you should seriously consider marriage.
再给瑞秋一次打扮得 像水果口香糖公主的机会
Give Rachel another chance to dress like Princess Bubble Yum.
小班在哪里
Where's Benny?
在这里
There he is!
小班在哪里
Where's Benny?
在这里
There he is!
小宝宝之所以学说话  大概是要叫大人闭嘴
That's probably why babies learn to talk, so they can tell grownups to cut it out.
我想问你个问题
Hey, I got a question for you.
小事情  别有压力
Just a little thing, no pressure.
好
Okay.
你有想过未来的规划吗
Do you ever, uh, think about the future?
当然有
Sure, I do.
是吗  包括我吗
Yeah? Am I in it?
甜心
Honey...
你就是我的未来
...you are it.
天啊  你今晚会很忙
Oh, God. You're about to get so lucky.
耶   耶
Yeah?  Yeah.
继续说  这个嘛…
Keep talking.  Well...
有时候我会想到卖掉诊所…
...sometimes I think about selling my practice.
我们搬到法国去
We could move to France.
做法国吐司
Make French toast. Ooh.
好  所以…
Okay, so...
我们在法国…
...we're in France...
做法国吐司
...and we're making the toast.
你看见角落有个小摇篮吗
Do you see a little bassinet in the corner?
你是指狗窝吗
Like a hound?
不是狗
Not a basset.
是婴儿摇篮
A bassinet.
你需要那个摇篮
You really need the bassinet?
我怕宝宝被狗压着
Well, I just think the baby would keep falling off the dog.
我们的未来里  难道没有小孩吗
Do you not see kids in our future?  Oh. Heh.
我喜欢小孩
I love children.
我有小孩
I have children.
我不想等70岁  小孩上大学后…
I don't wanna be 70 when our kids go off to college...
我们的生活才终于开始
...and our life can finally start.
听着
Hm. Look.
我想要你…
I want you...
现在
...now.
真好  我们现在不需要谈论这个
Well, that's great. We don't need to talk about this now.
反正还要很久很久
Really, I mean this is so, like, way, way, way in the future.
我现在聊气垫船跟猿人占领地球
I'm talking hovercrafts and apes taking over the planet. Heh, heh.
拜托你  钱德  我真的很想取得这个角色
Come on, Chandler. I want this part so much.
亲一个就好  我不会告诉别人的
Just one kiss. I won't tell anyone.
乔伊 不要就是不要
Joey, no means no.
嘿
Hey.
抱歉  你的羊不在我们这里
I'm sorry, we don't have your sheep.
瑞秋  我觉得你看起来很可爱
Aw, Rach, I think you look cute.
而你…
And you. You...
你…看起来好吃极了  离我远一点  我都说不要了
You, I could eat you with a spoon.  Get away from me. I said no.
理查按门铃  他在楼下
Richard buzzed. He's downstairs.
理查来了  我下去跟他道别
Richard's here? I should run down, say goodbye to him.
再见  祝你好运
Bye. Good luck.
你跟网络女友还顺利吗
How's your date with your cyber-chick going?
那是什么
Hey, what is all that?
古根汉美术馆的网站
It's a web site. It's the Guggenheim Museum.
她喜欢艺术…
She likes art...
我喜欢幽默
...and I like funny words.
〝握握〞是什么意思
What does she mean by "H.H."?
表示我们在牵手
It means we're holding hands.
你真的好可爱
Are you the cutest?
恐怕大概是吧
I'm afraid I might just be.
你这样全心全意对待一个人  我觉得真的很棒
I think it's so great that you're totally into this person...
但她有可能已经90岁  或是有两颗头
...yet for all you know, she could be 90 years old or have two heads.
还有可能是个男人
It could be a guy.
她不是男人好吗  我了解她
It's not a guy, all right? I know her.
有可能是大块头男子汉
It could be like a big, giant guy.
可恶  就差那么一点点  摩妮卡在后面踹了我一脚
Man, I got this close to him, and Monica kneed me in the back.
怎么了
What's going on?
我们在猜  钱德的女友是不是女生
We're wondering if Chandler's girlfriend is a girl.
问她会活多久
Ask her how long she's gonna live.
女人总比男人活得长
Women live longer than men.
你怎么没多跌两跤
How do you not fall down more?
好  问她用什么方法避孕
Okay, ask her what is her method of birth control.
好
All right.
〝我丈夫跟他的秘书上床〞
"My husband is sleeping with his secretary."
她结婚了
She's married?
至少我们确定她是女人了
At least we know she's a woman.
真不敢相信她结婚了
I can't believe she's married.
兄弟  我很遗憾
Oh, man, I'm sorry.
你一定很难过
This must be really tough for you.
我看过一篇文章  上面说婚礼上不该撒米…
I read this article that says you're not supposed to throw rice at weddings...
因为鸽子吃米会撑死它们的
...because when pigeons eat rice, it kills them.
难怪寿司店都看不到鸽子
That's why you never see pigeons in sushi bars.
瞧  我们这不是很开心吗  当然
See, we're having fun. Oh, absolutely.
我甚至没想到  我们不该想的那件事
I'm not even thinking about that thing that we're not gonna think about.
我也是
Neither am I.
嗨  你还好吗
Hey, there. Are you all right?
我在洗手间看见我上次婚礼爬出去的那个窗户
Yeah. But in the bathroom, I saw the window I crawled out of at my wedding.
天啊  我开始觉得自己真不该来
And, God, I just started thinking I shouldn't be here. I shouldn't.
大家看到我会评头论足  还会想到上一次的事
People are gonna be looking at me and judging me and thinking about the last time.
亲爱的  不会有事的  这是个婚礼
Sweetie, it's gonna be okay. It's a wedding.
一般来说  大家的焦点在新娘身上
Generally, people focus on the bride.
我知道  你说的对
I know, you're right.
好了  大家看我  很好
Alrighty. Everybody look at me. Good.
是时候了  伴娘  接待…
It's time. Bridesmaids and ushers...
请排成两列  谢谢
...let's see two lines. Thank you.
婚礼结束后见
I'll see you after the thing.
好  祝你好运   谢谢
Okay. Good luck. Thank you. Okay.
好
Okay.
哦
Ah.
你为什么不告诉我
Why didn't you tell me?
抱歉喔  你要我怎么做
What could I do?
站起来大叫 〝瑞秋  你屁股露出来了〞
Stand up and shout, "Hey, Rachel, your butt is showing!"
我的天啊  实在是太丢脸了
Oh, my God. This is so humiliating.
唯一更丢脸的  是我国二时…
The only thing that tops that was when I was in eighth grade...
我得在全校面前唱《科巴卡巴那》
...and I had to sing the "Copacabana" in front of the entire school.
才唱两句我就吓跑了
Two lines into it, I ran and freaked out.
天啊  我悲惨的人生再现眼前了
Oh, my God. My entire life's flashing before my eyes.
瑞秋  我记得那一次  其实也没那么糟
Rach, look, I remember that. It wasn't so bad.
罗斯  得了吧  你已经得到我了  我在跟你约会
Ross, would you stop! You got me. I'm dating you.
瑞秋
Rachel.
嗨  温伯老师  师母
Hi, Mr. Weinberg. Hi, Mrs. Weinberg.
很高兴再次看见你  亲爱的
It's wonderful to see you again, my dear.
事实上  我没想到会看见  这么精彩的事
In fact, I hardly expected to see so much.
你跟我说你什么也没看见  我跟你说过的事多的很
You told me you didn't see anything.  I tell you a lot of things.
很高兴看到你重新振作起来  亲爱的
Well, it's wonderful to have you up and about again, dear.
好好照顾自己
Stay well.
这是今天第三次  有人对我说这种话
That's the third time someone has said something like that to me today.
瑞秋  嗨
Rach! Hi.
我的天啊  我结婚了  对啊
Oh, my God, I'm married! I know!
我是巴瑞亨特法巴尔医师娘了
I'm Mrs. Dr. Barry Hunter, hyphen, Farber.
我真以你为荣  敏
I am so proud of you, Min.
敏
Min.
瑞秋  你还在啊
Oh, Rach. Still here.
上一次婚礼上  他们这时候正在打包碎鹅肝
At our wedding, they were packing up the chopped liver about now.
真有趣的故事
Yeah, I love that story.
我有个问题要问你们
Ahem. I have a question for you guys.
为什么大家一直说  很高兴见到我重新振作起来
Why do people keep saying it's good to see me up and about?
你逃婚后…
After you ran out on your wedding...
巴瑞的父母告诉大家你…
...Barry's parents told people you were sort of...
疯了
...insane.
疯了  因为得了梅毒
Insane?  From the syphilis.
什么
What?
不然你要他们怎么说   你不爱我了  怎么可能
What were they gonna say? You didn't love me anymore? Come on.
安琪拉
Angela?
乔伊崔比亚尼
Joey Tribbiani.
你今晚有事吗
Listen, what are you doing tonight?
我知道你在跟那男人交往  也许你可以带他过来…
I know you're seeing that guy. I was thinking maybe you could bring him...
喂   喂
Hello? Hello?
你要回她吗  她已经叮咚你第十次了
You gonna answer her? That's the 10th bing-bong message she's sent.
她想知道怎么回事  怎么回事  你结婚了
She wants to know what's wrong. What's wrong? You're married!
就是这么回事
That's what's wrong!
我的天啊
Oh, my.
怎么了  她想跟你碰面
What? She wants to meet you in person.
听着  菲比  我本来也很想跟她碰面
Look, Phoebe, I wanted to meet her in person too.
但她结婚了  她有丈夫
But she's married. She has a husband.
如果她丈夫不合适  而你才是合适的人呢
What if the husband is the wrong guy and you are the right guy?
这种机会不是天天都有
You don't get chances like this all the time.
如果你不跟她碰面  到80岁时  你会后悔得恨自己
If you don't meet her, you'll kick yourself when you're 80...
而且这件事难度很高  你会因此跌断屁股
...which is hard to do and that's how you break a hip.
好吧  我去见她
Okay. I'll do it.
太好了  快穿鞋  然后走出去见她
Okay, great! Put on your shoes and then march out there and meet her.
不  等等  你要先洗个澡  因为…
No, wait! You have to take a shower because ew!
我去拿…
And I'll get the...
不  你得先回她  先答应她
No, you have to answer her. Answer her first.
不  去煮点咖啡  因为这太令人紧张了
No, make some coffee because it's too much.
身材高大  棕褐色  年轻可爱
Tall and tan, and young and lovely
好  拜托嘛  再一次  这次我一定丢中
Okay, one more, please. I'm gonna get it in this time.
好  最后机会
Okay, last chance.
再次感到抱歉
Again, I'm sorry.
你知道吗   也许我不需要有小孩
You know what, maybe I don't need to have children.
也许我只是这样认为  因为这个社会…
Maybe I just think I do because that's what society...
也就是我妈
...and by that I mean my mom...
总是说服我…
...has always convinced me that I...
But I want her so badly
说我需要有小孩
I do.
我一定要有小孩  很抱歉  但我真的很需要
I have to have children. I'm sorry, I just do.
各位请注意
Yo, could I have your attention?
伴郎要敬酒
Best man making a toast here.
谢谢大家
Thank you. Ahem.
我还记得巴端与瑞秋  初次约会回家
I remember when Barry got home from his first date with Rachel.
恩
Huh?
怎么  你可以请了同一个乐团  我就不能用相同的演讲稿
What? You hired the same band. I can't use the same speech?
谢谢  感谢各位
Thank you. Thank you very much.
总而言之  祝两位…
Anyway, I wish you both...
幸福美满
...a wonderful life together. Aw.
还有  瑞秋
And, Rachel.
什么事  不  我是百分之百认真的
What? No, no, in all seriousness.
没有几个女人有胆量回到这里
Not a lot of women would have the guts to come back here.
更别提光着屁股回来
And even fewer who'd do it with their asses hanging out.
就这样
That's it.
我想  啊  补充一下
I'd like to add something to that.
补充什么…  没关系的  好的
What are you adding? What are you adding?  It's okay. It's okay.
多数人不认得我  我是瑞秋的男友
Most of you don't know me. I'm Rachel's boyfriend...
我的老天爷啊
Oh, dear God.
罗斯
...Ross.
我只想说…
And I'd just like to say that...
今晚瑞秋鼓起很大的勇气前来
...it did take a lot of courage for Rachel to come here tonight.
我要郑重声明…
And just for the record...
她不是因为得了梅毒才逃婚
...she did not run out on Barry because she had syphilis.
你在干嘛  我是认真的
What are you doing? I'm serious.
她之所以逃婚…
The reason...
很简单  是因为…
...she walked out on Barry is simply that...
她不爱他
...she didn't love him.
当然也意外的便宜了我
Which, incidentally, worked out pretty well for me. Heh, heh.
干杯
Cheers.
停车场见  不  瑞秋
See you in the parking lot.  No, Rach.
她又逃了
And once again, she is out of here!
好  谁赌九点四十五分
Okay, who had 9:45? Hm?
嘿
Heh.
你知道吗   巴  我不走了
You know what, Bar? I'm not gonna leave.
也许我该走  但我不走
I probably should, but I'm not.
我答应自己至少要全程参加  你其中一场婚礼
I promised myself I'd make it through at least one of your weddings.
今晚  我只想撑过去…
Tonight, all I wanted was to make it through this evening...
带着一点优雅与尊严
...with a little bit of grace and dignity.
我想我们都希望当什么事都没有发生过
Well, I guess we can all agree that's not gonna happen.
我想我也没什么话好说
I guess there's nothing really left to say...
除了…
...except...
她的名字叫萝拉
Her name was Lola
她是歌舞女郎
She was a showgirl
黄色羽毛
With yellow feath...
插在她头上
Feathers in her hair
还穿着性感小洋装
And a dress cut down to there
她会跳…
She would...
默朗格舞  默朗格舞
Merengue  Merengue
谢谢你  亲爱的
Thank you, honey.
还会跳恰恰
And do the cha-cha
她想成为明星  汤尼总是看顾酒吧
And while she'd like to be a star Tony always tended bar
等等
Wait, wait!
大家一起唱
Everybody!
科巴…
Copa
科巴卡巴那
Copacabana
是哈瓦那最带劲的地方
The hottest spot north of Havana
在科巴
At the Copa
科巴卡巴那
Copacabana
音乐与热情是科巴的主流
Music and passion were always In fashion at the Copa
There's a somebody I'm longing...
好吧
Okay.
我愿意
I'll do it.
愿意什么
You'll do what?
如果要我和你生孩子  就生吧
If kids is what it takes to be with you, then kids it is.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
如果有必要  我愿意再重来一遍
If I have to, I'll do it all again.
我会早上四点起来喂奶
I'll do the 4:00 feeding thing.
我会去育儿培训班
I'll go to the PTA meetings.
我会当足球队教练
I'll coach the soccer team.
真的吗  如果有必要的话
Really? Yeah, if I have to.
摩妮卡…
Monica...
我不想失去你
...I don't wanna lose you.
如果一定要重来一遍…
So if I have to do it all again...
那么我愿意
...then I will.
你真是太好了
You are the most wonderful man.
如果你没有说…
And if you hadn't have said...
17次〝如果我一定要〞
..."If I have to," like, 17 times...
我一定会说 〝好  我们生小孩吧〞
...then I'd be saying, "Okay, let's do it."
但你不打算这么说
But you're not.
天啊  我都不敢相信  我要想说的是
Oh, my God. I can't believe what I'm getting ready to say.
我想要有小孩
I wanna have a baby.
但我不想和一个不愿生的人一起生
But I don't want to have one with someone who doesn't really want to have one.
天啊
God.
我爱你
I love you.
我知道你爱我
I know you do.
我也爱你
Me too.
现在怎么办
So what now?
我想我们…
I guess we just...
继续跳舞
...keep dancing.
Someone to watch
Over me
她在哪儿  她在哪儿
Where is she? Where is she?
对了  我有个问题
Oh, hey, I have a question.
她在哪儿
Where is she?
钱德  放轻松  钱德  她会来的
Chandler. Relax, Chandler. She'll be here.
就是她
Oh, oh, oh. That's her.
对啊  人生有这么美好
Yeah, because life's just that kind.
钱德  你不能一直盯着门看
PHOEBE: You gotta stop staring at the door...
那就像盯着水壶看
...like a watched pot.
如果你一直看  门永远不会沸腾
If you keep looking at it, the door's never gonna boil.
我想你应该要做的是不要…
I think what you have to do is try not to...
噢  我的天啊
Oh, my God.
噢
Oh...
我的…
...my...
天啊
...God.
噢
Oh...
我的…
...my...
天啊
...God.
好吧
All right.
我觉得很愧疚  因为我想做个好兄弟
I've been feeling incredibly guilty because I wanna be a good friend.
管他的  我是个好兄弟  闭上嘴再闭上你的眼睛
And damn it, I am a good friend. So shut up and close your eyes.
喔
Wow.
你真是个好兄弟
You are a good friend.
试镜今早试过了  只是我没被选上
The audition was this morning, and I didn't get it.
但你这吻确实够劲
But that was a hell of a kiss.
瑞秋真幸运
Rachel is a very lucky girl.